MOHPREET KAUR

mohpreet.kaur8@gmail.com ◆ Cell +1 249-288-7290 ◆ https://mohpreetk.github.io/

CAREER SUMMARY

Experience 1+ years as Software/Web Developer(Academic) and Data Analyst(HealthTech)

1+ years dealing with clients and customers.

Languages Swift, C#, Java, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (ES 2020), TypeScript, PHP, DAX **Tools** XCode, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, MySql Workbench, FileZilla, SSMS,

Acode, visual stadio, visual stadio code, mysqi vvoikbelleli, i liezilia,

Azure, Android Studio, IntelliJ, PowerBI

Frameworks Entity, Angular, React, Bootstrap

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Regional Municipality of York

Newmarket, ON

09/2021 - 12/2021

Data and Analytics Technician **Technologies**: PowerBI, DAX, M

- Successfully reworked and launched the Region's Hospital Performance Dashboard providing the user 70% more information expanding from 4 Sheets to around 9 interlinked sheets.
- Increased the report interactivity and organized the data in a more logical order.
- Set up the report for automatic refreshes for timely and efficient updates.
- Completed the work term and received a pass grade on my transcripts

Georgian College Barrie, ON

Peer Mentor 12/2020 - 12/2021

- Streamlined the program processes and represented the team at different events which helped in increasing program enrollment by nearly 170%.
- Worked with the team to find solutions to complex problems/unanswered questions.
- Maintained confidentiality and privacy of mentees and secured their personal information.

Cell N Computer Mississauga, ON

Customer Sales Representative

04/2021 - 12/2021

- Communicated with the customers and negotiated the cost and timelines.
- Documented the record of products dropped in for repair, making sure the forms are filled and signed properly.

Projects

Memory Master

05/2021 - 08/2021

Technologies: XCode, Swift, MacInCloud, Storyboard, Interface Builder

- Individually worked on a tile match game applying the fundamentals of Swift, MVC, and OOP.
- Documented requirements, process flows, and presentations for the user.

Decor and Handicraft Merchant

01/2021 - 04/2021

Technologies: ASP.NET C#, Visual Studio, Azure, Entity, Razor Pages, Stripe, APIs, HTML/CSS/JS, MSSQL, SSMS

- Reproduced a shopping cart website to list and sell products.
- Used ASP Identity and Authorization for User Authentication and Login IDs.

Education & Accreditations

Undergraduate Diploma in Computer Programming

Barrie, ON

Georgian College

01/2021 - 12/2021

- Secured overall GPA of 96.37/100 with Dean's List
- International Student Leadership Award & Board of Governor's Medal Award